floridajobs.org 2016-12-12

# Department Privacy Statement - FloridaJobs.org

Thank you for visiting the Department of Economic Opportunity website. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit the Department of Economic Opportunity website, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. 

When you visit the Department of Economic Opportunity website, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved, and your personal information is not identified.

If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form with personal information, the information will be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's archiving policies. However, information will not be disclosed to third parties or other government agencies, unless required by state or federal law. Please note that Florida's public records law requires that all information received in connection with state business be made available to anyone upon request, unless the information is subject to a specific statutory exemption.

If you have other questions about this privacy policy, or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please feel free to e-mail us at [DEO_comments@deo.myflorida.com](mailto:DEO_comments@deo.myflorida.com), or contact us by telephone at 850-245-7105.
